Am I supposed to write what I'll be
doing for the next ten years?
Life in 1918.
That's a long time.
I'll have my teacher's certificate, no
doubt.
And be happily married with two
children.
None of whom will bear any resemblance
to Felix, mind you.
Some future.
What about you, Sarah?
What'll you do?
I don't really know.
You certainly won't have to worry.
You'll be rich one day when you inherit
father's fortune.
You won't have to do anything.
Sarah will have plenty to do.
Tease with celebrities, date dinners,
travel to exotic places, shopping.
If I were rich, I'd do nothing. But
you're not.
My father won't let me do nothing.
Idle hands make for idle wit.
Felix is proof of that.
I certainly don't intend to be idle.
What do you intend to do anyway?
You could support me with my profession.
What profession?
To become rich.
This is going to be my future. It's
going to be dreadfully dull.
Well, by the time you come into your
inheritance at age 21, well, by then
be fully prepared to comprehend the many
investments which have been and will
continue to be made on your behalf. So,
with good planning and attention to
detail, well, you'll be rewarded with
the kind of life that most people only
dream about.
Oh, come now.
These decisions affecting the next
quarter have to be made right away so
can send our response to Montreal by
cablegram.
Now, where did I put that particular
about the American oil?
Oh.
Oh, here's something, yes.
Jonathan? Jonathan!
Constable Watercover.
What? I simply don't know where you
disappear to sometimes, Jonathan. You
off at the most critical moment. Yes,
Auntie. I try my best and you try my
patience.
That painting should be moved away from
the radiator. It will be damaged by the
heat. Sir?
The painting damaged by the heat.
Thank you. I'll inform the manager.
There will be no gallivanting here.
The future of the Blackwell fortune,
your fortune, Jonathan, is at stake.
This venture into an electric company is
a new departure for us.
Property, shipping, now those are all
solid investments.
The power, I ask you, a commodity you
can't even see.
However, now that you've dragged me
here, I expect you to attend to the
in hand and forget all this nonsense
about antiquities. Come along.
Gentlemen.
I wish to introduce you to my nephew,
Jonathan Ravenhurst Blackwell.
Sarah, what's wrong?
You seem somewhat downtrodden today.
I don't know.
It's just she's got my whole life
planned out for me.
It's really appalling.
I can't even repeat it to you.
With your inheritance, you should just
leave Avonlea and travel wherever you
like. Make it sound so glamorous and
easy.
Hardly think it'll ever be that way,
though.
I'm tied to Aunt Hattie.
She is trying to do the right thing.
Felix feeds this animal.
Felix is those that do the work that
reap the rewards.
That's why I have other ways of earning
money.
I'm taking things in this town that I
can find that no one else needs to a
dealer. Well, I suppose one man's
rubbish is another's treasure.
I am not going to let this bother me.
And it's very important that I decide on
a career.
If my father's advisors have their way,
I'll set up a finishing school in
Switzerland, drowning in reports from
trustees and lawyers.
I know what I'd do with all that money.
Spend it on meaningless items and
ridiculous things.
Sarah, why don't you make a list of all
the things you like to do, and something
will come clearly out of it. Yes.
For example, think of some activities,
thank you, that you could do for a long
period of time without them feeling like
a punishment.
Thank you, Aunt Janet.
No boobsy?
I think that is a splendid idea.
Please, Aunt Olivia.
I've made a list of my options.
Things I really, really enjoyed doing
and writing came out on top.
Maybe it's hereditary.
Sarah, I don't own the paper. I can't
just hire you like that.
I have to prove to Aunt Hattie that I
can actually achieve something if she'll
just take my ideas seriously.
Yes, well, you'd have to prove to Mr.
Tyler that you can write if you wanted
work here.
Honestly, Sarah, no one says that you
have to do everything Aunt Hattie tells
you. Look, if they don't like the story
I write, they don't have to print it.
And it doesn't have to be that big an
article.
Look, I know so much about objets d 'art
and antiques.
I own plenty of them myself.
Aunt Olivia, I am the perfect person to
write this story.
How am I ever supposed to find my place
in the future if no one will let me
explore the possibility?
Sarah, all right.
You can cover the antique show with me.
But I am not making any promises, all
right? We'll just have to sit down and
discuss it with Mr. Tyler when he comes
back in a few days.
Thank you, Aunt Olivia.
I also had a carpet bag, sir.
Oh, dear, sir.
Possibly fell off between here and the
station.
I'll go back along the road and take a
look for it.
You're staying at the White Sands? Yes,
sir.
I'll find it.
Very good. I'm much obliged.
Ah, good dog.
Good dog.
Here, Tigger.
No, no, no. No harm done, young lady.
Well, I'm sorry to disturb you.
Who are you?
Oh, forgive my manners.
Gerald McDougall Young.
Antiques and objets d 'art.
Mr. Young, we've been anticipating your
arrival.
Yes. I'm Olivia Dale of the Avonlea
Chronicle. How do you do?
How do you do?
I was hoping that we could arrange an
interview with you. We thought it would
fine publicity for your upcoming
valuation.
Thank you.
No.
Publicity is something I do not seek.
But if you could impart directions to
the White Sands Hotel, Mr... Pike.
Pike. Gus Pike.
Gus Pike.
And your charming companions.
Oh, well, as they can. Mr. Young, I'm
Sarah Stanley.
I'm Mrs. Dale's assistant.
I was also planning on covering the
valuation.
If you could grant me one small
interview, just so that I could let the
know about all the alluring treasures
found lurking in the cellars of Avonlea,
it wouldn't have to be so much publicity
as an informative feature for our
community.
I would rather we wait and discuss the
proposed article until after I'm
Oh, look, I'm on my way to the hotel,
and I'm sure to be late if I don't
so why don't I take you then? That would
be very good. Let's see.
It's half past twelve. I'll join you if
you don't mind.
Ladies, please to make your
acquaintance.
And Miss Stanley, we'll meet again after
my work here is completed.
Lead on, Gus Pike.
All good.
Thank you.
So, should we look for the other bag,
then? No, let the coach operator do
There's nothing of value in any case.
Come on.
I wonder, would it be possible for an
introduction to Miss Stanley's parents?
Those pearl earrings she was wearing
were quite rare.
Oh, Sarah's got no parents.
She lives with her aunt, Miss Hattie
King. A parable of manners and civility.
Her other aunt, Olivia Dale, is the one
who introduced herself as working at the
Chronicle. I see.
And I gather from her dress and her
jewelry that Miss Stanley is not a
this vicinity.
Oh, no. She's from Montreal.
Montreal, really?
Stanley, not Mr.
Blair Stanley of Stanley Imports and
Trading Company?
Sarah's father passed away two years
ago.
Left Sarah the entire fortune.
Oh, I see. I've got your key.
Is there anything amiss, sir? Oh, not at
all. Not at all, sir.
Exquisite.
Absolutely exquisite.
France. 18th century Omeru clock signed
by Mr. J. Link.
And that magnificent piece of furniture.
Empire mahogany and tulip wood
escritoire.
Lovely.
Thank you. I know, sir.
And this is a very handsome work indeed.
Ah, it should be.
Brought from my ancestral manor in
Scotland.
It's Italian.
It's Tiepolo.
It's a fake.
Of what?
That quality of cadmium yellow.
Not used till the 18th century.
But a very fine forgery in every other
respect.
Now, don't that beat all.
Well... Oh, Mr. Young, of course.
Please excuse my lack of diplomacy.
We were expecting you.
And quite.
That work will still fetch you a very
pretty penny, mind you.
Oh, uh, suite number nine, Mr. Young.
Mr. Pike, see the young gentleman to his
room. Right away, sir.
Perhaps you'd like to work for me while
I'm staying here, Gus Pike. Make some
extra pocket money.
Excuse me, sir.
Excuse me.
I need someone to keep a record of all
items sold and given for restoration at
this valuation.
I'll make it worth your while, Gus Pike.
Oh, you can count on me, Gerald. Good.
These will be very exciting moments.
watching and waiting for those truly
magical items.
Well, it sounds pretty dull to me, going
around looking at everybody's old pots
and pans.
No, no, you see, that's what makes it so
exciting.
It's a treasure hunt.
Families collect and save all manner of
nicks and nacks, but among them are a
priceless few created with love,
objects...
The treasure hunt to be conducted with
great discretion and away from prying
eyes. Thank you very much, ladies from
the Chronicle.
You mean to say in my very house, even
the junk in my own room could be worth a
fortune? Quite possibly.
Now, if you'll excuse me. Oh, wait.
Sorry.
I think I'll go home and do a bit more
good scrounging. Excuse me.
Excuse me. Well, Sarah, that's a good
start.
Next, Mr. Birkpot and a pair of
andirons.
These end irons were truly superb, Mr.
Potts.
Made in a forge by a local craftsman,
were they?
No, they were made by the blacksmith.
A craftsman. A man who loved iron.
Oh, yes.
People will pay a respectable sum for
these.
In 50 or 100 years.
I'm truly sorry.
Long time to wait, I'd say.
Mark. Mrs. Eulalie Bugle and a pair of
silver candlesticks.
Eulalie Bugle.
Paul Revere, Boston, 1768.
Oh, no, no, no.
Put these down. I didn't bring them for
you to paw over them, Gus Pike.
A hallmark appears to be here.
But? If you'll allow me, Mrs. Bugle, I'd
like to clean these up and study them
at greater length.
Would that be all right with you?
I suppose so.
If they truly are by the renowned
silversmith Paul Revere. What do you
My family had to flee the American
Revolution with only the clothes on
back.
And these priceless treasures.
I concur, madam.
The beauty in the design alone is beyond
value.
Just how much beyond value?
For coin silver of this vintage, I would
say approximately...
$1 ,000.
You'll give me a receipt, of course.
Of course.
You may return tomorrow, Mrs. Bugle, for
my full appraisal.
Well, ladies and gentlemen, that
concludes my time here today.
Gus Pike will be good enough to catalog
all of your property.
This evening, I shall spend evaluating
each lot, and you may return tomorrow
my full appraisal. And notes!
On items I wish to purchase.
Good day. Thank you.
Mr.
Young. Mr. Young, I'm very sorry to
disturb you. I'm sorry to disturb you,
Stanley. People say they find you very
entertaining and very informative, too.
You seem to know volumes about so many
things.
However, did you come to know so much
about the world and antiques?
Study and observation.
Surely antiques is a rather lonely life,
Mr. Young.
You're confined in an old shop full of
dusty antique things and... Oh, no, no,
no, no. To the contrary, Mrs. Dale.
It is my passion.
Antiques are an exciting adventure.
See here.
I once found a map to buried treasure on
the Galapagos.
It was hidden in a secret drawer of a
Japanese chest.
Almost cost me my life at the hands of
cutthroat pirates who were after it.
But a king's ransom was ultimately
retrieved.
Mr. Young, I'd very much like to arrange
that interview we spoke of.
I'm sorry, but I really don't enjoy
speaking with the press.
But you have been so charmingly
persistent.
Perhaps you and Mrs. Dale would care to
have dinner with me here at the hotel
tonight. Oh, that's very kind. We'd love
to. Good. Shall we say six then?
Six would be fine.
Six it shall be.
Bye -bye.
I'll be back momentarily. Be a good
brother and tidy up some of the better
pieces. Sure thing.
Mrs. Bugle's going to have my hide.
You said there's a hotel near this town
of Avonlea, driver.
I'd like to investigate whether or not
my nephew may be there.
Are you there, my man?
Me, madam?
To whom else would I be talking?
How may I help you? It remains to be
seen whether you can be of any help to
whatsoever. I have travelled across the
godforsaken island looking for my
nephew. It seems to be the sort of semi
-reputable halfway establishment that he
might... Frequent. You think he may be a
guest at the hotel, madam? That is what
I wish to discover.
The name is Blackwell Jonathan
Ravenhurst Blackwell.
I'm afraid, madam, there is nobody by
that name in our registry book. Are you
absolutely certain?
May I help you, ladies?
Oh, yes.
We're to meet Mr.
Gerald Young for dinner.
We're conducting an interview.
Oh, of course.
You may wait here, or perhaps you would
prefer the dining room.
Hello, Sarah and Olivia.
Excuse me, Mr. Tremaine.
Is Mr.
Young in?
I've got some wonderful things, I mean
antiques, that he should really take a
look at. I don't approve of staff,
Master King, hobnobbing with guests.
But look!
Where did you find that bag?
Uh, I don't exactly remember.
I've been everywhere.
It could have been at the old Ancaster
barn or... or maybe alongside the road,
like it looked like it was thrown into a
ditch.
Felix, what have you been doing?
Looking for objects of art, buried
treasure.
See here, J .R .B., Jonathan Ravenhurst
Blackwell.
And these are his clothes.
Where is my nephew?
I pray he's not met with some foul play.
You must show me the exact location on
the road, boy.
I intend to contact the police.
I intend to stay here and get some
answers.
Felix, gather up all these things right
away.
Let me show you, Madam, what I may be
able to offer you for accommodation.
We want to see him.
I want to speak to that so -called
antique dealer.
Mr. Young is in sweet night. Felix King,
mind your business. Now, please, Mrs.
Buell, everyone, just a moment.
Look, where is he, Gus Pike?
I just tried to check the company listed
on his card. Why, that telephone number
doesn't even exist.
He's a fraud.
Well, he told me he was only going out
for a few moments.
He must still be in a hotel somewhere.
Made off with my silver, no doubt.
Oh, I don't think he'd do something like
that, Mrs. Bugle.
He must be in here somewhere.
Just what do you know about this, Gus?
Me?
Nothing, nothing.
What would I know about silver?
Took off for a moment. My precious
thousand -dollar candlesticks have been
pilfered. I'll be back with the
constable.
Out of my way.
I intend to offer a substantial reward
for any information concerning my
Constable. Make use of your entire fort.
Gower the countryside for him. Well,
let me review the facts. Now, where did
you lose him, Lady Blackwell? We were in
Charlottetown for a meeting regarding a
local business enterprise.
He was there one minute and gone the
next.
He does that with some frequency, but on
this occasion, he did not reappear. How
could you allow such charlatans to set
up here, Mr. Tremaine?
Antique dealer, indeed.
He's gone.
Without paying his bill, hasn't he?
Told you so. If you'll allow me to
finish searching the entire premises,
Bugle, maybe I can turn up your
candlestick.
What's that antique fellow's name?
Young?
That's him.
Disappeared into the night like a thief.
Took the only thing of value.
My Paul Revere candlesticks.
Oh, dear.
What's that?
Those aren't mine. He's stolen mine.
What's this, then?
Give it to me.
It's Jonathan Shue.
See, his initials and the shoemaker's
name.
Well, it all falls into place now,
doesn't it?
It's possible that this personage, Mr.
Gerald Young, has done away with your
nephew, ma 'am.
I refuse to believe that without further
evidence.
What about the vast fortune I lost to
that swindler?
Constable, I know my nephew has
disappeared, but the question is where.
We must organize a search party
immediately. No stone must be left
Come along, Mrs. Bugle. Leave this
matter with the law.
Can you shed any light on these
proceedings, Mr. Tremaine?
Me?
Well...
Truth be told, I saw Gus Pike with that
very silver, Mrs. Bugle, and it came to
me that he was very friendly with the
antique dealer.
I shall simply have a word with him.
Not as friendly as Mr. Young was with
Sarah Stanley and Olivia Dale, so I hear
tell. Are they related to that king boy
who showed us the spot on the road?
Felix King, yes.
And an employee of this hotel.
Peaks could be so exciting.
Now she thinks that Blackwell was
murdered?
That Gerald Young was definitely up to
something. Well, I thought for certain
was legitimate.
Mr. Young is a professional.
And so am I.
There must be some explanation.
And no one even seemed to care that you
took that bag.
I thought they wanted to keep it for
evidence.
Well, I guess I'm no more of a
professional reporter than you are,
What a wild goose chase.
Doesn't everyone want to know about the
murder?
Not unless it's your own.
Is mother and father asleep? Of course.
Where have you been all evening?
Looking for Gerald Young, who's
disappeared.
Now there's talk of a missing person.
He can't just have disappeared.
He didn't even have the manners to leave
a note at the desk. He never paid his
bill. He just completely vanished.
Well, never mind. It seems as though
you've stumbled onto a delicious story.
That's true, Sarah. Mr. Tyler would be
awfully impressed if you could make a
good piece out of him.
Something critical might link these two
figures together.
As reporters, we have to figure out what
it is.
I'm staying up. Why don't you help me
with my quilting? You can tell me all
about it.
Oh, no, Flissy, I have got to leave.
Well, Jasper will be fit to be tied.
I've left him at home all afternoon and
evening with that baby.
I'll just say good night.
Good night,
Angela. Good night.
I'll admit it to you, Felicity.
I found Gerald Young very intriguing.
Very bookish, but very masculine.
Why was he just passing through?
He didn't actually steal anything.
Why would he invite us to dinner and
then not show up?
And this whole disappearance of the
black valet.
Felix calls it foul play.
Don't be ridiculous, Sarah. Felix has
never been right about anything for as
long as I've known him.
He just likes the idea of murder and
intrigue because he reads so many
potboilers.
And here.
Well, that's it, eh?
Mr. Young, what are you doing here? I
caught him sneaking away from here.
The murderer!
Now, don't you move a muscle, Mr. Gerald
Young. If you'll only agree to hear me
out, I promise. Why should we listen to
you, huh?
Yeah! What were you doing with the shoes
of the missing Jonathan Blackwell? And
where did you see the last heir?
And what were you... Keep an eye on this
one.
Please, Sarah. I'm really not such a bad
son.
I just came back from my things. My bag
must have fallen off the coach. I think
we should all hide.
Why don't you just let them in?
Please, Sarah.
I'm asking you to believe in me.
Please, help me. I beg of you.
What do you think you're up to, Gus?
Come along, then.
Sarah, what are you doing? Just pretend
you don't know anything. He isn't here.
Oh, there he is.
I'm terribly sorry to disturb the King
household at this hour. Just what do you
think you're up to, Gus Pike?
And where are your parents?
If you will excuse me, young lady.
These are not my candlesticks, Gus Pike.
The disappearance of the Blackwell heir
takes precedence over the disappearance
of your so -called heirloom.
Need we delay any longer, Constable?
Arrest this young man. What on earth is
going on?
What are all you people doing here?
Will you, young ragamuffin, kindly tell
me...
Gerald Young, you swear to me you
haven't done anything underhanded to
Blackwell's nephew.
I swear to you that Jonathan Ravenhurst
Blackwell is alive and well, but I
am sworn to secrecy as to his present
whereabouts.
Trust me, all will be revealed in due
course.
Please, tell me the whole story
exclusively.
Yes.
If you let me go free.
I'll meet you at the train station
tomorrow at noon.
I'll confide everything I know to you
then.
I want Gus Pike questioned in the
disappearance of my sister. And I want
questioned in the disappearance of my
nephew.
Gus Pike, you're under arrest as an
accomplice in the disappearance of one
Gerald Young and two Jonathan Ravenhurst
Blackwell.
You must let me go free before I can
give you a story.
You have caused everyone a great deal of
anxiety, Gerald Young. Or should I say
Jonathan Blackwell?
If my aunt ever found out about this, I
would be forever under her scrutiny.
She's been like a mother to me, and I
love her dearly, and she's devoted
to my well -being.
and to the preservation of my estate,
but my poor Aunt Edith, she has
no passion for the things that excite
me.
What do you do with it all? You just
purchase antique?
Oh, Sarah, you don't comprehend.
I give them life.
What do you mean?
I can't put paint to canvas or even pen
to paper.
With my inheritance.
So you mean that the wealthy must
support the work of the artist?
Yes. And that's why I love things and
the people who made them.
Sarah, you too were born to a life of
privilege. I knew it from the moment I
you. But without people like you and I,
just quite possibly, there might not be
a Michelangelo, a da Vinci.
I never really thought of an inheritance
in quite that way before.
Yes, it's an obligation. It's a duty.
And so, Gerald Young, you pursue what
you love.
And as Jonathan Ravenhurst Blackwell,
you do what you must.
Precisely.
You're eager to stay with me, Jonathan,
but you must try to be less infatuated.
Oh, no.
World of antiques.
It's a world fraught with mystery and
adventure.
Milady. Thank you.
Who committed this insolence?
For Jonathan's relief, $5 ,000.
He'd been abducted.
I want to know who perpetrated this
outrage and why you allowed the culprit
slip through your fingers.
I found it in Lady Blackburn's mail slot
so that I took it upon myself to
deliver it.
Calm yourself, my lady. We will call the
constable again and meet him in Mr.
Gerald Young's room.
There must be something we've all
overlooked.
Don't worry, madam. I have an idea your
nephew will be restored to you. I
certainly hope so.
Otherwise, I shall have this entire
establishment torn apart, board by
need be.
And who are you, sir?
Aha!
Of all the impotence.
You, madam, are the aunt of the
unfortunate young man who has
Yes, but how do you... You wear an
antique pin with the letters E .B.
scripted in diamonds, proclaiming your
relation to the Blackwell family.
Yes, that is so.
Furthermore...
I can see that you have been preoccupied
for days now, Miss, such of your
nephew.
Your shoes, madame, betray some day's
wear, with several nicks on the heels
the toes, telling me you've been
traveling in great haste.
Your attire.
Hmm.
Berets of Knightsbridge.
Show some signs of travel in an open
-air carriage.
Steams upon your right arm and the hem
of your dress.
Who are you?
Doyle E.
Reichenbach, private investigator of the
farm Plimpton and Plimpton on the trail
of one Gerald McDougall Young.
And I believe you, young lady, have had
the misfortune of his acquaintance. And
you, madam, have received word from the
nefarious villain that note that you
clutched your heart, your pained
expression.
Oh, Mr. Reichenbach.
You are the only one who can truly help
me.
Yes.
Ransom note.
How outrageous.
Indubitably.
Lady Blackwell, you shall comply with
the ransom demands.
Five thousand dollars? Mind your own
business. Mr. Reichenbach, if you can
discover the whereabouts of my nephew
and apprehend the culprit, I shall draw
out a cashier's check for that amount.
Very good, madam.
But, um, how do you think you'll
accomplish this?
In my hand, I hold the clue.
And we shall father this clue while it
is still hot!
may release the unfortunate Guth Pike.
Oh, yes.
What grounds, Mrs. Bugle's evidence
alone? He is yet another innocent dude.
But Guth, all right.
The lad may return to his job.
See here, Constable. I shall prove it to
you within the hour.
Upstairs, on the floor, there is residue
of silver plating and plaster of Paris.
The pieces of silver plating are in the
style of Paul Revere prior to the
Revolutionary War.
The Bugle candlestick. I would hazard to
say that the original reviews were sold
by the family.
Probably making a hasty retreat
following the British defeat.
I could have told her that, that Harrod
and Mrs. Bugle. Silver indeed.
Never fear, madam.
I shall have your nephew safely returned
within the hour.
Come, Stanley.
The game is afoot.
Sarah, Stanley, what is going on here?
Sarah, personally, I find you're keeping
all this secret outrageous.
Stanley!
I just love all this murdering and
mysterious mayhem.
Well, what do you think this inspector
will find?
Maybe the body's stuffed in a trunk.
Honestly, Felix, you're acting like a
morbid fool.
But I really think that you and Sarah
owe Gus an apology for dragging him into
all of this.
Well, what if they don't find anything?
You'll get all the blame. Oh, calm down,
Flickity.
Has anyone fed Digger?
Who fed Time?
I dragged myself into this, Felicity.
Besides, Nate and Jill's good for what
ails you.
I'm only worried no one's convinced Mrs.
Buechel.
Hello, everybody. Sarah.
Gerald Young, what are you doing here?
This is Jonathan Ravenhurst Blackwell.
What?
And Gerald Young.
And Doyle E. Reichenbach.
Mrs. King, Mrs. Dale.
I'm afraid I owe your family a grave
apology.
I've caused a great deal of trouble.
Especially for you, Mr. Gus Pike.
I definitely will never lay my hands on
another antique as long as I live.
Mrs. Bugle still wants my head on a
silver platter.
She's the sort of bad lucks who'll get
her, too.
Yes, well... You may give her this.
With compliments from Mr.
Gerald Young.
This ought to ease Miss Bugle's vengeful
nature.
Gee.
Gerald.
Um, Mr. Young, do you think we could
still get that interview with you?
Miss Stanley has all the details. I'm
sure she'll write the story the public
wants to hear.
And Felix King.
Oh, no need to reward me, Gerald.
That dish you hold in your hand.
Worth the king's ransom in case you
didn't realize.
The dog's dish.
Severus Porcelain from France.
Late 18th century.
Now.
might want to submit it to an
independent auctioneer for his
Who exactly are you?
Felix, give it to me. You can't be
trusted. I had it first, Felicity.
Give it back! Felix, give me that!
Like you said, Gerald, the world of
antiques is full of greed and tragedy.
Antida! You naughty, naughty boy,
Jonathan.
You gave me such a fright, you'll put me
into an early grave.
I'm heartily sorry, Aunt.
I'm beginning to suspect you're trying
to get rid of me.
How can you say that, Aunt Edith?
I adore you.
But where is the redoubtable Doyle E.
Reichenbacher?
Why, he has disappeared.
On the trail of that insidious criminal,
Gerald MacDougall Young.
and in gratitude for all he undertook on
my behalf, I rewarded him with the
ransom money.
Innocent as doves, cunning as serpents.
Well, have it your way.
And what, young lady, has my nephew been
telling you for your gossip column?
Why, nothing of any importance.
I quite agree with you. Come, Jonathan.
Yes, Van Dieter.
Local constabulary believe that Mr.
Blackwell's captor, Mr. Gerald Young,
long since left Avonlea and P .E. Island
for exotic parts unknown.
Special investigator Mr.
Doyle Reichenbach remains devoted to the
pursuit of this known criminal.
Mrs. Eulalie Bugle has been mysteriously
compensated for the loss of her family
heirloom to the amount of $1 ,000.
Wonderful, Sarah.
It's much better than my dreary
composition.
Mr. Tyler is practically ready to offer
her a position.
Thank you, Angelivia.
It is good. You know, I think the
authorship must run in the family.
Oh, definitely.
But then our Sarah is obliged and
destined to lend her attentions to more
important matters.
Perhaps. But I have decided you were
right, Aunt Hetty.
I should take a closer interest in all
these business matters.
Besides, my inheritance represents a
great responsibility and obligation to
future.
Mr.
Blackwell, do come in.
No, no, no, no. I can't, Miss Stanley.
I'm afraid I can't tarry in Avonlea much
longer.
My aunt plans to incarcerate me at
Oxford.
Just imagine.
All the treasures of the realm and
continent at my fingertips.
Well, I think that Jonathan should keep
a very close eye on Mr. Gerald Young.
Jonathan, come along.
We'll miss the train and I won't have
you disappearing again.
Don't excite yourself, Aunt Edith.
However...
Gerald McDougal Young might just well
return.
He owes you dinner.
I am much obliged.
And I to you.